A Guide to the Taconic Foundation records FA407
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1958-2010; 1; 76.73 Cubic Feet 172 document boxes (including 1 half-box), 2 oversized flat boxes; 2.02 Gigabytes 35 digital files
  - Public Education Association: General
    - 1995-1996 (Box 125, Folder 1234)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 125, Folder 1235)
      - Parents' Guide to Mathematics, Science, and Technology Education in New York City Public Schools (Brochure), 1997; 2014:FA407:017 (Box 210, Item 2014:FA407:017)
    - (Literature), 1989-1990, 1993-1995 (Box 125, Folder 1236)
      Includes "Making Big High Schools Smaller: A Review of the Implementation of the House Plan in New York City's Most Troubled HIgh Schools," January 1989.
    - (Literature), 1992-1993 (Box 125, Folder 1237)
      Includes PEA reports on "Small Schools and Savings: Affordable New Construction, Renovation and Remodeling" and "Small Schools' Operating Costs: Reversing Assumptions about Economies of Scale," both December 1992.
  - Public Education Association: Bridge Project
    - 1959-1962 (Box 125, Folder 1238)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 125, Folder 1239)
    - (Literature), 1961-1963 (Box 125, Folder 1240)
  - Public Education Association: Committee for the Education of Pregnant School-Age Girls, 1966, 1968-1971 (Box 125, Folder 1241)
  - Public Education Association: Open Doors
    Support for School-Business Partnership project, under the direction of Frances (Mrs. Robert) Low.
    The Open Doors program established a partnership between schools and businesses, to introduce students to occupational choices and facilitate the transition from school to work. Frances Low received project funding from the Taconic Foundation in 1968-1969 to investigate and report on training and counseling programs in the New York City Public Schools and on methods of relating local business organizations to the schools. Open Doors was at first jointly sponsored by the Public Education Association and the New York Urban Coalition, and then from 1970 up to 1974 solely by the Public Education Association. The Economic Development Council assumed sponsorship in 1974. For later material, see files on Economic Development Council of New York City: Open Doors.
    - 1970-1971 July (Box 125, Folder 1242)
    - 1971 August - 1973 (Box 126, Folder 1243)
    - (Literature), 1972 (Box 126, Folder 1244)
      Open Doors School-Business Partnership Conference and Exhibit, January 20, 1972.
    - (Literature), 1978 (Box 126, Folder 1245)
      File contains "Evaluation Report: Open Doors," by Dellora H. Hercules, 1978. The Taconic Foundation commissioned this report.
  - Public Education Association: Vocational Training and Guidance Project
    - 1962 (Box 126, Folder 1246)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 126, Folder 1247)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 126, Folder 1248)
    - 1967-1970 (Box 126, Folder 1249)
  - Public/Private Ventures: General
    Corporation for Public/Private Ventures.
    - 1977-1978 June (Box 126, Folder 1250)
    - 1978 July-December (Box 126, Folder 1251)
    - 1979 (Box 127, Folder 1252)
    - 1980 (Box 127, Folder 1253)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 127, Folder 1254)
    - 1984-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 127, Folder 1255)
    - 1989 (Box 127, Folder 1256)
    - 1990-1994 (Box 127, Folder 1257)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 127, Folder 1258)
    - 1998 (Box 128, Folder 1259)
  - Public/Private Ventures: Marc Freedman, 1988-1989 (Box 128, Folder 1260)
    File contains 1989 correspondence and Freedman's August 1988 draft of "Fostering Intergenerational Programs for At-Risk Youth" ("Partners in Growth"). For correspondence prior to 1989, see files for Public/Private Ventures: General.
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 1983-1991 (Box 128, Folder 1261)
    Correspondence file.
  - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1971-1977 (Box 128, Folder 1262)
  - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1996-1997, 1999-2000 (Box 128, Folder 1263)
    Materials from 1996 and later are from Accession 2012:089.
    Support for Williamsburg Fair Housing and Census 2000 projects. The Williamsburg class-action suit was originally litigated by Brooklyn Legal Services Corporation A.
  - Putney School, Inc., 2004-2006 (Box 128, Folder 1264)
    Endowment fund named in memory of Michael S. Currier, to provide financial aid for low-income minority students.
  - Quayle, Dan, 1984 (Box 128, Folder 1265)
    Request on behalf of the Hudson Institute's Center on Education and Employment Policy.
  - Queens College, Institute for Community Studies, 1968-1969. 1981 (Box 128, Folder 1266)
    Support for study and conferences on Community Controlled Schools, partially funded by the Institute for Community Studies. Materials from 1981 consist of a proposal for a gun-control study.
  - Radcliffe College, Audrey and Stephen Currier Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1967-1999 (Box 128, Folder 1267)
  - Real Estate Research Corporation (Urban Affairs Project), 1969 (Box 128, Folder 1268)
    Project file. Consultancy for Daniel Patrick Moynihan, as head of Urban Affairs Council; and recommendations on possible involvement of Urban America in stimulating suburban housing integration.
  - Real Great Society, 1967-1969 (Box 129, Folder 1269)
    East Harlem youth group. Support for Urban Planning Studio.
  - Regional Plan Association: General Program
    - 1961-1965 (Box 129, Folder 1270)
    - 1966-1971 (Box 129, Folder 1271)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 129, Folder 1272)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 129, Folder 1273)
    - 1979 (Box 129, Folder 1274)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 129, Folder 1275)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 129, Folder 1276)
      These materials mainly concern the RPA's Bridging the Social Chasm program.
    - 1996-1998 (Box 129, Folder 1277)
      This material mainly concerns the Workforce and Community Development program outlined in the Association's Third Regional Plan.
      - A Region at Risk: The Third Regional Plan for the New York – New Jersey – Connecticut – Metropolitan Area, by Robert D. Yaro and Tony Hiss, 1996; 2014:FA407:059; 1 bound volume (Item 2014:FA407:059)
    - (Literature), 1978, 1986 (Box 129, Folder 1278)
      Includes draft of 1978 report on Housing Segregation in the Tri-State Region.
  - Regional Plan Association: Breezy Point, 1963-1975 (Box 130, Folder 1279)
    - Map of Gateway National Recreation Area, 1971; 2014:FA407:018 (Box 210, Item 2014:FA407:018)
  - Regional Plan Association: Choices for '76 Project
    The project was originally entitled "Priorities for 1976."
    - 1971 (Box 130, Folder 1280)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 130, Folder 1281)
  - Regional Plan Association: Friends of Gateway, 1987-1989 (Box 130, Folder 1282)
    Grant to help launch the Friends of Gateway as an independent organization working in support of Gateway National Recreation Area. See also the files for Regional Plan Association: Gateway Citizens Committee.
    - Friends of Gateway brochure, 1988; 2014:FA407:019 (Box 210, Item 2014:FA407:019)
  - Regional Plan Association: Gateway Citizens Committee
    Established in June 1970, the Gateway Citizens Committee advocated on behalf of Gateway National Recreation Area as an urban national park and worked to ensure the protection and preservation of the lands surrounding New York Harbor. The Gateway project was one of the Taconic Foundation's longest-running grants.
    For the origins and early funding of the Gateway project, see the file for Regional Plan Association: Breezy Point. For later materials see also Regional Plan Association: Friends of Gateway.
    Files for 1986-1988 include materials relating to the Friends of Gateway and to the Regional Plan Association's Open Space and Transit on Track projects.
    Later materials for 1988-1989 (pertaining mainly to the Bridging the Social Chasm program) and for 1996-1997 (pertaining to the Workforce and Community Development project) have been separated and are refiled under Regional Plan Association: General Program.
    - 1973-1975 June (Box 130, Folder 1283)
    - 1975 July - 1976 February (Box 130, Folder 1284)
    - 1976 March-April (Box 130, Folder 1285)
    - 1976 May-December (Box 130, Folder 1286)
    - 1977 January-May (Box 131, Folder 1287)
    - 1977 June-December (Box 131, Folder 1288)
    - 1978 January-May (Box 131, Folder 1289)
    - 1978 June-December (Box 131, Folder 1290)
    - 1979 (Box 131, Folder 1291)
    - 1980 (Box 131, Folder 1292)
    - 1981 (Box 131, Folder 1293)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 131, Folder 1294)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 131, Folder 1295)
    - 1986 (Box 132, Folder 1296)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 132, Folder 1297)
  - Regional Plan Association: Gateway Citizens Committee (Literature)
    - 1960-1976 (Box 132, Folder 1298)
    - 1978-1984 (Box 132, Folder 1299)
      - Map, Gateway National Recreation Area - General Management Plan, 1979; 2014:FA407:020 (Item 2014:FA407:020)
      - Draft Environmental Statement, General Management Plan, DES 78-6, Gateway National Recreation Area, New York/New Jersey, 1978; 2014:FA407:021 (Box 210, Item 2014:FA407:021)
  - Regional Plan Association: Charles McKim Norton Education Fund Steering Committee, 1977-1981 (Box 132, Folder 1300)
  - Regional Plan Association: Stanley Tankel Fund, 1969 (Box 132, Folder 1301)
  - Renewal Committee in Harlem
    Architects' Renewal Committee in Harlem (ARCH).
    - 1965 (Box 132, Folder 1302)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 132, Folder 1303)
  - Renewal Magazine, 1965, 1968-1970 (Box 132, Folder 1304)
    Renewal magazine was a publication of the Chicago City Mission Society. The file includes three issues from 1968-1970.
  - Retarded Infants Services, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 132, Folder 1305)
  - Retarded Infants Services, Inc., 1962-1968 (Box 132, Folder 1306)
  - Rheedlen Centers for Children and Families. See Harlem Children's Academy, Inc.
  - Robinson, Armstead L., 1969-1971 (Box 132, Folder 1307)
    Project file. Support for a comparative review of African American Studies programs.
  - Rocking the Boat, Inc., 2002-2006 (Box 133, Folder 1308)
    From Accession 2012:089.
  - Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt Institute, 1990-1993 (Box 133, Folder 1309)
    Support for Model/Better Schools Program, especially at P.S. 151 in Manhattan.
    - Afterschool Program at P. S. 151, 1991 May; 2014:FA407:042; 3 still images (Item 2014:FA407:042, Item data_value_missing_ee27c57ba34279d4677551432ccdc4b0)
  - Rouse Company: General, 1967-1971, 1974, 1976, 1979 (Box 133, Folder 1310)
  - Rouse Company: Smokey House Farm Study, 1968-1971 (Box 133, Folder 1311)
    Project file. The Rouse Company was engaged to study the economic and recreational potential of Taconic's Smokey House Farm property in Danby, VT.
  - Rouse Company: Social Development Conference Center, 1963-1966 (Box 133, Folder 1312)
    File of correspondence and reports concerning conference center proposed for Columbia, Maryland.
  - Russian Ballet, 1965-1966, undated (Box 133, Folder 1313)
    File contains certificate of authenticity concerning Picasso's work on a curtain for the ballet "Le Train Bleu"; Russian Ballet Development Limited, Inventory of costumes and decorations for the Original Ballet Russe; and List of Musical Scores, Diaghilev and de Basil Ballet Foundation.
    There is no indication of why this file is found among the Taconic Foundation records. The Victoria and Albert Museum purchased the Picasso curtain at auction in 1968.
  - Sacred Heart Parish, 1968 (Box 133, Folder 1314)
    San Francisco, CA.
  - Saint Mary's Neighborhood Project (Community Action Program). See South Bronx Community Council.
  - San Francisco Planning and Urban Renewal Association (SPUR), 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 133, Folder 1315)
    - SPUR information booth in Union Square, 1966; 2014:FA407:043; 2 still images (Item 2014:FA407:043)
  - Scherman Foundation, 1980-1983, 1988-1992 (Box 133, Folder 1316)
  - Scholarship, Education and Defense Fund for Racial Equality: General
    Formed in 1962 as the Congress of Racial Equality Scholarship, Education, and Defense Fund (CORE-SEDF), the fund became known as the Scholarship, Education and Defense Fund for Racial Equality (SEDFRE) in 1966.
    - 1963-1965 (Box 133, Folder 1317)
    - 1966 (Box 133, Folder 1318)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 134, Folder 1319)
    - 1970-1973 (Box 134, Folder 1320)
      - SEDFRE economic development work in Greene County, Alabama, 1971; 2014:FA407:044; 3 still images (Item 2014:FA407:044)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 134, Folder 1321)
  - Scholarship, Education and Defense Fund for Racial Equality: Gary, Indiana, Project, 1969-1970 (Box 134, Folder 1322)
  - School – Industry Liaison Service
    The School – Industry Liaison Service was a project originally undertaken by Frances Low in conjunction with the New York Urban Coalition and the Public Education Association.
    - 1968-1969 (Box 134, Folder 1323)
    - 1970 January-June (Box 134, Folder 1324)
    - 1970 July - 1971 (Box 134, Folder 1325)
  - Schools for the Future Systems and Materials Corporation
    Support for Primary Education Project, conducted by Thomas R. Mansfield, and proposal for an experimental School for the Future in New York City under the direction and following the methods of Caleb Gattegno.
    - 1964-1965 July (Box 134, Folder 1326)
    - 1965 August - 1966 (Box 134, Folder 1327)
  - Second Good Hope Baptist Church (New Orleans), 1968 (Box 134, Folder 1328)
    Grant for Thugs United, in recognition of the youth group's contribution to the improvement of urban life.
  - Settlement Housing Fund
    Settlement Housing Fund was created in 1969 as a housing development arm of United Neighborhood Houses.
    - 1971 (Box 134, Folder 1329)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 135, Folder 1330)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 135, Folder 1331)
    - 1976 (Box 135, Folder 1332)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 135, Folder 1333)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 135, Folder 1334)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 135, Folder 1335)
    - 1984-1986 (Box 135, Folder 1336)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 135, Folder 1337)
    - 1990-1996 (Box 136, Folder 1338)
    - (Literature), 1989, 1995 (Box 136, Folder 1339)
      Includes 1995 "Study of Rent-to-Income Ratios and Income Limits and Eligibility Standards in Government Assisted Housing."
  - Sillin, Lelan F., Jr., 1968-1969 (Box 136, Folder 1340)
    Correspondence file. Sillin chaired an Urban America committee that studied ways to increase interaction between urban youth groups and business and civic leaders.
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1963, 1966-1969 (Box 136, Folder 1341)
    - Smithsonian Building with spotlights, circa 1967; 2014:FA407:045; 1 still image (Item 2014:FA407:045)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1970-1973 (Box 136, Folder 1342)
  - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital, 1966-1968 (Box 136, Folder 1343)
  - Soifer, Avi (Mini-School Study), 1972 (Box 136, Folder 1344)
    Project file. Taconic-commissioned paper on School Space Study and mini-schools in New York City.
  - South Bronx Community Council (St. Mary's Neighborhood Project), 1961 (Box 136, Folder 1345)
    Grant in support of the New York City Community Action Program, St. Mary's Neighborhood Project.
  - South Bronx 2000 Local Development Corporation
    South Bronx 2000 Local Development Corporation was a non-profit community organization that ran housing preservation, community development, and recycling projects in South Bronx neighborhoods.
    - 1982-1983 (Box 136, Folder 1346)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 136, Folder 1347)
    - 1986 January-May (Box 136, Folder 1348)
    - 1986 June-December (Box 137, Folder 1349)
    - 1987 (Box 137, Folder 1350)
    - 1988 January-June (Box 137, Folder 1351)
    - 1988 July-December (Box 137, Folder 1352)
    - 1989 (Box 137, Folder 1353)
    - 1990 (Box 137, Folder 1354)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 137, Folder 1355)
    - 1993 (Box 137, Folder 1356)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 137, Folder 1357)
      - Big City Forest display of Reclaimed Wood Products, circa 1995; 2014:FA407:046; 1 still image (Item 2014:FA407:046)
    - 1996 (Box 137, Folder 1358)
    - 1997 (Box 137, Folder 1359)
  - South Carolina Council for Human Rights
    Prior to 1973 the council was known as the South Carolina Council on Human Relations.
    - 1969-1971 (Box 138, Folder 1360)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 138, Folder 1361)
  - Southern Center for Human Rights
    - 1993-2003 (Box 138, Folder 1362)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 138, Folder 1363)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 138, Folder 1364)
    - 2008-2009 (Box 138, Folder 1365)
  - Southern Cooperative Development Fund
    The organization was originally founded as the Southern Consumers' Cooperative.
    Materials for 1969-1970 concern a request for investment and technical assistance from the Cooperative Assistance Fund.
    - 1964-1966 (Box 138, Folder 1366)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 138, Folder 1367)
  - Southern Courier, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 138, Folder 1368)
    Three file copies of The Southern Courier were discarded in processing. The discarded issues were volume 4, numbers 31, 45, and 46, dated August 3-4, November 9-10, and November 16-17, 1968.
  - Southern Education Program
    In July 1967 the Southern Teaching Program merged with Recruitment of Southern Teachers to form the Southern Education Program, Inc.
    Materials prior to 1968 pertain to the Southern Teaching Program.
    - 1964, 1966-1967 (Box 138, Folder 1369)
    - 1968-1971 (Box 138, Folder 1370)
  - Southern Education Reporting Service, 1968-1969 (Box 138, Folder 1371)
    Correspondence concerning the proposed listing of the Taconic Foundation in a "Directory of Resources on Race."
  - Southern Regional Council: General Program
    - 1958-1964 (Box 139, Folder 1372)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 139, Folder 1373)
    - 1968-1974 (Box 139, Folder 1374)
    - 1975 (Box 139, Folder 1375)
    - 1976 (Box 139, Folder 1376)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 139, Folder 1377)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 139, Folder 1378)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 139, Folder 1379)
    - 1985 (Box 140, Folder 1380)
    - 1986 (Box 140, Folder 1381)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 140, Folder 1382)
    - 1990 (Box 140, Folder 1383)
    - 1991 (Box 140, Folder 1384)
    - 1992 (Box 140, Folder 1385)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 140, Folder 1386)
    - 1995 (Box 140, Folder 1387)
    - 1996-1997, 2001 (Box 140, Folder 1388)
  - Southern Regional Council: Conference of Black Elected Officials
    Sponsored by the Voter Education Project, the Southwide Conference of Black Elected Officials convened in Atlanta, GA, in December 1968.
    - 1968 (Box 141, Folder 1389)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 141, Folder 1390)
  - Southern Regional Council: Evaluation of Southern Teaching Program and Mississippi Study Project, 1965 (Box 141, Folder 1391)
    File mainly concerns expense payments; it does not contain the study reports.
  - Southern Regional Council: Housing Program, 1973-1975 (Box 141, Folder 1392)
  - Southern Regional Council: Operation Opportunity, 1964 (Box 141, Folder 1393)
    "Operation Opportunity" tested compliance in the South with Title II provisions of the Civil Rights Act outlawing discrimination in public accommodations.
  - Southern Regional Council: Reports, 1964, 1988-1990 (Box 141, Folder 1394)
    File contains various SRC publications, including report on Day Labor Pools and Temporary Employment, Change through Education, and annual report for 1988.
  - Southern Regional Council: State Councils on Human Relations, 1960-1969 (Box 141, Folder 1395)
  - Southern Regional Council: Voter Education Project
    - 1961-1962 (Box 141, Folder 1396)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 141, Folder 1397)
    - 1965-1966 June (Box 141, Folder 1398)
    - 1966 July-December (Box 141, Folder 1399)
    - 1967-1971 (Box 142, Folder 1400)
  - Southern Regional Council: Voter Education Project (Congressional Correspondence), 1969 (Box 142, Folder 1401)
    File concerns letter from Taconic Foundation president John Simon to the Senate Finance Committee, October 1, 1969, protesting provisions in the pending tax-reform bill, which would adversely affect foundation support of voter education programs.
  - Southern Regional Council: Voter Education Project (Leadership Training Program for Black Law Students), 1969-1970 (Box 142, Folder 1402)
  - Southern Regional Council: Voter Education Project (Reports), 1966-1970 (Box 142, Folder 1403)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 1404)
  - Special Service for Groups, Inc. (Sons of Watts), 1968 (Box 142, Folder 1405)
  - Spence-Chapin Adoption Service, 1960-1967 (Box 142, Folder 1406)
  - State Communities Aid Association, 1967, 1969-1970, 1982, 1988 (Box 142, Folder 1407)
  - Stern, Mark, 1984-1986 (Box 142, Folder 1408)
    Research on black voter registration.
  - Stern Family Fund (General Correspondence), 1973-1986 (Box 142, Folder 1409)
  - Stern Family Fund (Historic New Orleans, Inc.), 1966-1967 (Box 142, Folder 1410)
    Support for project to improve highway planning.
  - Stillman College, 1965-1970 (Box 142, Folder 1411)
    Support for political education program.
  - Student Interracial Ministry, 1966-1967 (Box 142, Folder 1412)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, 1960-1961, 1965 (Box 142, Folder 1413)
  - Student/Sponsor Partnership, 1994-1997 (Box 143, Folder 1414)
  - Suburban Action Institute: General
    Paul Davidoff and Neil Gold founded and directed the Suburban Action Institute. In 1980 the organization became the Metropolitan Action Institute.
    For later materials see files for Metropolitan Action Institute.
    - 1968-1970 April (Box 143, Folder 1415)
    - 1970 May - 1971 (Box 143, Folder 1416)
    - 1972-1973 June (Box 143, Folder 1417)
    - 1973 July - 1974 (Box 143, Folder 1418)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 143, Folder 1419)
    - 1977-1981 (Box 143, Folder 1420)
  - Suburban Action Institute: Board Material - Grant Memos, 1969-1980 (Box 143, Folder 1421)
  - Suburban Action Institute: Candlewood Lake, WatersEdge, Sherman (CT), 1973-1974 (Box 144, Folder 1422)
    Controversy over proposed WatersEdge development project, on Candlewood Lake, in New Fairfield, CT. Correspondents include Malcolm Cowley.
  - Suburban Action Institute: Personal, 1969-1971, 1973-1974 (Box 144, Folder 1423)
    File contains various memos between Jane Lee Eddy and John Simon, meeting notes, and a few pieces of correspondence.
  - Suburban Action Institute: Press Clippings, 1969-1972 (Box 144, Folder 1424)
  - Suburban Action Institute: Press Clippings, 1973-1978 (Box 144, Folder 1425)
  - Suburban Action Institute: Press Releases, 1970-1972 (Box 144, Folder 1426)
  - Suburban Action Institute: Press Releases, 1973-1980 (Box 144, Folder 1427)
  - Suburban Action Institute: Reports and Literature
    - 1971-1972 (Box 144, Folder 1428)
      Feasibility analysis for proposed development in Mahwah, NJ, March 1971; volume 2 of "A Survey of Attitudes toward Government Assisted Moderate and Low Income Housing in Westchester County, New York," December 1972; 1972 audit report; and descriptive brochure for proposed Ramapo Mountain development.
    - 1971-1974 (Box 144, Folder 1429)
      Copies of legal briefs and decisions.
    - 1976 (1 of 2) (Box 144, Folder 1430)
      Coalition for an Equitable Region report on its first year's activities, May 1975-May 1976.
    - 1976 (2 of 2) (Box 144, Folder 1431)
    - 1976-1979 (Box 144, Folder 1432)
      Mary Brooks testimony on Community Development Block Grant Program, 1976; Regional Equity newsletter, 1976-1979.
  - Suburban Action Institute: Research Reports
    These research reports formed an appendix to the Suburban Action Institute's May 17, 1974, "Progress Report" to the Taconic Foundation. Studies concern employment, commutation, and housing in the New York metropolitan area; an analysis of Suffolk County, New York; and research in support of the Institute's litigation program.
    - (Sections 1-2), 1973 May - 1974 May (Box 145, Folder 1433)
    - (Section 3), 1973 May - 1974 May (Box 145, Folder 1434)
    - (Section 4), 1973 May - 1974 May (Box 145, Folder 1435)
  - Suffolk Housing Services